VLADI FELDMAN

Frond-End Developer

- Vladi-feldman
- ✓ <u>Vladi.fel@gmail.com</u>
- 0547691227
- Nahalat Yetzhak 18, Tel-Aviv
- in <u>vladif</u>

SKILLS

- Front-End development using JavaScript,
 TypeScript, React,
 Redux, jQuery, HTML &
 CSS,
- Unit & Functional tests using Jest & Enzyme
- UX/UI design, Material-UI, Storybook
- **E2E Automation**, Testing Methodologies.
- Perforce, Git, JIRA, Agile
 & SCRUM methodologies

EDUCATION

- Tel-Aviv University, 2008-2011
 - B.Sc. Geophysics & Geography
- Tel-Aviv University,
 2012-2018
 M.Sc. Geophysics

LANGUEGE

English – Highly Proficient Hebrew – Native Speaker Russian – Native Speaker

PROFILE

Meticulous and highly motivated front-end developer with 2+ years of experience in building web apps. Proficient with **JavaScript**, **Typescript**, **React**, **Redux**, **CSS**, **HTML**.

Problem-solving oriented and highly determined. Loves the challenge and exploring new ventures.

Quick learner and great team player, with high attention to details and passion for **UX/UI**, looking to embark on a new journey.

EXPERIENCE

Bright Machines, Jan 2021 – Present

Software and robotics company whose applications focus on automation for the electronics manufacturing industry.

- Front-end Engineer
 - Working in close collaboration with back-end and UX/UI teams on one of the core applications, following a strict release and delivery schedule.
 - Developing and maintaining a shared UI components library used company wide.

Emerson (Paradigm), Mar 2012 – Dec 2020

Enterprise technology company specializing in software solutions for the oil & gas industry.

- Front-end Developer, Aug 2018 Nov 2020
 - Working as part of a Next-Gen group developing a hybrid desktop & web application that handles workflow building and large-scale mathematical operations.
 - Working in close collaboration with product and design teams on new feature development from user-story to a complete working component.
 - Converting UX/UI mockups into fully-functioning React components.
 - Extensive work with Material-UI components and style guidelines
 - Working in Agile/ Scrum development cycles
 - CI/CD working methodologies
- Automation Developer, Mar 2015 Aug 2018
- QA Applications Geoscientist, Mar 2012 Mar 2015

References will be given upon request